1.	Run at speed to the far end of the arena past the end marker and do a left rollback – no hesitation. 
	2.	Run to the opposite end of the arena past the end marker and do a right roll- back – no hesitation. 
	3.	Run past the center marker and do a sliding stop. Back up to center of the arena or at least ten feet (three meters). Hesitate. 
	4.	Complete four spins to the right. Hesi- tate. 
	5.	Complete four and one-quarter spins to the left so that horse is facing left wall or fence. Hesitate. 
	6.	Beginning on the left lead, complete three circles to the left: the first circle large and fast; the second circle small and slow; the third circle large and fast. Change leads at the center of the arena. 
	7.	Complete three circles to the right: the first circle large and fast; the second cir- cle small and slow; the third circle large and fast. Change leads at the center of the arena. 
	8.	Begin a large fast circle to the left but do not close this circle. Run straight up the right side of the arena past the center marker and do a sliding stop at least twenty feet (six meters) from wall or fence. Hesitate to demonstrate the com- pletion of the pattern.  Rider must dismount and drop bridle to the designated judge.

